"Double Helix"
"الحلزون المزدوج"
Bro...
أخ...
I... I can't feel my legs.
أنا... لا أشعر بساقي.
I'm never going to walk again, am I?
لن أستطيع المشي مرة أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
Don't say that.
لا تقل ذلك.
This is just a small town.
هذه مجرد بلدة صغيرة.
Once we get to a bigger hospital,
بمجرد وصولنا إلى مستشفى أكبر،
they can run more thorough tests.
بإمكانهم إجراء اختبارات أكثر شمولاً.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Cheng Yi-chen, it's going to be okay.
تشنغ يي تشن، سيكون كل شيء على ما يرام.
Don't be scared.
لا تخف.
So... which hospital are we going to?
إذن... إلى أي مستشفى سنذهب؟
What about Mom?
وماذا عن أمي؟
I'll take care of Mom.
سأعتني بأمي.
No matter which hospital you go to,
بغض النظر عن المستشفى الذي تذهب إليه،
you just listen to what Qin Lang says.
ما عليك سوى الاستماع إلى ما يقوله تشين لانغ.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
This is a hospital.
هذا مستشفى.
Don't cause a scene.
لا تُثير ضجة.
What are you going to do?
ما كنت تنوي القيام به؟
Why are you so worked up?
لماذا أنت متوتر للغاية؟
You tell me.
أخبرني أنت.
You need to calm down.
عليك أن تهدأ.
How are you going to hurt me?
كيف ستؤذيني؟
What is it now?
ما هو الوضع الآن؟
Xiao Chen.
شياو تشن.
He said Cheng Yi-chen's legs are broken.
وقال إن ساقي تشنغ يي تشن مكسورتان.
That can't be right.
لا يمكن أن يكون هذا صحيحاً.
He's lying to me, isn't he?
إنه يكذب عليّ، أليس كذلك؟
I just came here to apologize to her.
لقد جئت إلى هنا لأعتذر لها.
I didn't know she...
لم أكن أعرف أنها...
Mom!
أم!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Get a doctor!
استشر طبيباً!
Doctor! Doctor!
يا دكتور! يا دكتور!
Get out.
اخرج.
Get out of here right now.
اخرج من هنا الآن.
Xiao Chen, I swear I didn't mean for this to happen.
شياو تشن، أقسم أنني لم أقصد أن يحدث هذا.
Let me explain.
دعني أشرح.
I really...
أنا حقاً...
I just want to take responsibility, Xiao Chen.
أريد فقط أن أتحمل المسؤولية يا شياو تشن.
Listen to me. I'm calling the police.
اسمعوني. سأتصل بالشرطة.
Someone's causing a disturbance at the hospital.
هناك شخص ما يُحدث اضطراباً في المستشفى.
(Episode 8: Fine, let's break up.)
(الحلقة 8: حسناً، فلننفصل.)
Cheng Yi-chen! Cheng Yi-chen!
تشنغ يي تشن! تشنغ يي تشن!
Mom.
أم.
Is your brother really paralyzed?
هل أخوك مصاب بالشلل فعلاً؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
Qin Lang is already abroad,
تشين لانغ موجود بالفعل في الخارج.
finding a good doctor for him.
إيجاد طبيب جيد له.
Don't you worry.
لا تقلق.
He'll be fine.
سيكون بخير.
Xiao Chen, my sister arranged for my release.
شياو تشن، أختي، رتبت لإطلاق سراحي.
I have to go to the US
يجب أن أذهب إلى الولايات المتحدة
to sign the papers renouncing my inheritance.
لتوقيع الأوراق التي أتنازل فيها عن ميراثي.
Tomorrow is the deadline.
غداً هو الموعد النهائي.
I'll come back for you.
سأعود إليك.
I'll do everything I can
سأبذل قصارى جهدي
to heal Cheng Yi-chen's legs.
لعلاج ساقي تشنغ يي تشن.
[Blocking Lu Feng's contact info]
[حجب معلومات الاتصال الخاصة بلو فنغ]
Ma'am.
سيدتي.
Please, don't get up.
من فضلك، لا تنهض.
Are you Cheng Yichen's girlfriend?
هل أنتِ حبيبة تشنغ ييتشن؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'm Cheng Yichen's girlfriend.
أنا حبيبة تشنغ ييتشن.
Good.
جيد.
It's good you have a girlfriend.
من الجيد أن لديك حبيبة.
Cheng Yichen, will you marry me?
تشنغ ييتشن، هل تقبلين الزواج بي؟
I think you need a fresh start.
أعتقد أنك بحاجة إلى بداية جديدة.
Don't you want to put your mother's mind at ease?
ألا تريد أن تطمئن والدتك؟
Give yourself
امنح نفسك
a new chance.
فرصة جديدة.
Okay?
تمام؟
You know Lu Feng better than I do.
أنت تعرف لو فنغ أفضل مني.
Sooner or later, he'll come back and find you.
عاجلاً أم آجلاً، سيعود ويجدك.
But I can help you.
لكن يمكنني مساعدتك.
Cheng Yichen, why didn't Zhuo Lan come today?
Cheng Yichen، لماذا لم يأتي Zhuo Lan اليوم؟
Is she angry?
هل هي غاضبة؟
No, Mom.
لا يا أمي.
She had something else to do today.
كان لديها شيء آخر لتفعله اليوم.
Cheng Yichen.
تشنغ ييشن.
Listen to your mother.
استمع إلى والدتك.
Snap out of it.
استفق من غفلتك.
A good girl like Zhuo Lan...
فتاة طيبة مثل تشو لان...
is one in a million.
هو واحد من بين مليون.
Mom, eat first.
أمي، تناولي الطعام أولاً.
Cheng Yichen.
تشنغ ييشن.
I'm dying.
أنا أموت.
Don't you get it? I'm dying.
ألا تفهم؟ أنا أموت من الضحك.
Please, just take pity on me.
أرجوكم، ارحموني.
Don't make the same mistake again.
لا تكرر نفس الخطأ مرة أخرى.
I'm begging you.
أتوسل إليك.
Xiao Chen.
شياو تشن.
Mom.
أم.
Zhuo Lan and I are getting married.
أنا وزو لان سنتزوج.
Really?
حقًا؟
Getting married is good.
الزواج أمر جيد.
It's good to get married.
من الجيد الزواج.
Mr. Cheng Yichen,
السيد تشنغ يتشن،
do you take Ms. Zhuo Lan to be your wife?
هل تقبل السيدة تشو لان زوجةً لك؟
I do.
أفعل.
Ms. Zhuo Lan,
السيدة تشو لان،
do you take Mr. Cheng Yichen to be your husband?
هل تقبلين السيد تشنغ ييتشن زوجاً لكِ؟
I do.
أفعل.
Please exchange the rings.
يرجى استبدال الخواتم.
I have to go back and find him.
عليّ أن أعود وأجده.
Lu Feng, what on earth are you trying to do?
لو فنغ، ما الذي تحاول فعله بحق الجحيم ؟
I need to get the story straight.
أحتاج إلى توضيح القصة.
He couldn't have done this.
لم يكن ليتمكن من فعل ذلك.
Find him?
هل وجدتموه؟
You've gotten older, but you haven't gotten any smarter.
لقد كبرت في السن، لكنك لم تصبح أكثر ذكاءً.
Do you think it's that easy to find someone?
هل تعتقد أن العثور على شخص ما بهذه السهولة؟
With the Zhuo family's power and influence, hiding someone is child's play for them.
بفضل قوة ونفوذ عائلة تشو، فإن إخفاء شخص ما هو أمر سهل للغاية بالنسبة لهم.
Lu Feng, I'm telling you,
لو فنغ، أقول لك،
you're not going anywhere today.
لن تذهب إلى أي مكان اليوم.
I've already signed the agreement.
لقد وقّعت الاتفاقية بالفعل.
Right now, the Lu family and I...
في الوقت الحالي، أنا وعائلة لو...
have absolutely nothing to do with each other.
لا علاقة لهما ببعضهما البعض على الإطلاق.
If I want to find him,
إذا أردت أن أجده،
that's my own business.
هذا شأني الخاص.
You have no right to control me.
ليس لك الحق في التحكم بي.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
I said you have no right to control me.
قلتُ لكَ ليس لكَ الحق في السيطرة عليّ.
Are you out of your mind?
هل فقدت عقلك؟
He's already married.
هو متزوج بالفعل.
And he did it behind your back.
وقد فعل ذلك من وراء ظهرك.
He doesn't love you at all.
إنه لا يحبك على الإطلاق.
You're throwing away your future,
أنت تضيع مستقبلك،
your family,
عائلتك،
all for a man like that?
كل هذا من أجل رجل كهذا؟
That's my business.
هذا شأني الخاص.
Sis.
أخت.
I suddenly realize...
أدركت فجأة...
you're just like Dad.
أنت تشبه أبي تماماً.
I just really...
أنا حقاً...
really love him.
أحبه حقاً.
Just go.
انطلق.
Go.
يذهب.
Let him go.
دعه يذهب.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I've contacted my friends.
لقد تواصلت مع أصدقائي.
Their hospital is very experienced.
مستشفاهم يتمتع بخبرة كبيرة.
They'll definitely be able to cure Cheng Yi-chen.
سيكونون قادرين بالتأكيد على علاج تشنغ يي تشن.
Qin Lang.
تشين لانج.
I'm leaving Cheng Yi-chen in your hands.
أترك تشنغ يي تشن بين يديك.
As for my mom,
أما بالنسبة لأمي،
I'll be here.
سأكون هنا.
She just needs to focus on getting better.
كل ما تحتاجه هو التركيز على التعافي.
Okay.
تمام.
Is that Xiao Chen?
هل هذا شياو تشن؟
Mom.
أم.
It's me, Xiao Chen.
أنا شياو تشن.
Why are you so thin?
لماذا أنتِ نحيفة جداً؟
My son.
ابني.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Mom.
أم.
Cheng Yi-chen.
تشنغ يي تشن.
Your mother... she's gone.
والدتك... لقد رحلت.
There's no point in you going back now.
لا جدوى من عودتك الآن.
Cheng Yi-chen.
تشنغ يي تشن.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
You did great on your exams, son.
أحسنت في امتحاناتك يا بني.
You've made me so proud.
لقد جعلتني فخوراً جداً.
Great, just great.
رائع، رائع حقاً.
That's my boy.
هذا ابني.
Son, come and eat.
يا بني، تعال وكُل.
Life right now...
الحياة الآن...
is like a fast-paced, illogical, black-and-white dream.
يشبه حلماً سريع الإيقاع، غير منطقي، أبيض وأسود.
My hardworking father,
والدي المجتهد،
my caring mother,
أمي الحنونة،
my little brother who adored me.
أخي الصغير الذي كان يعشقني.
When did they all just... disappear?
متى اختفوا جميعاً فجأة؟
Once we get to the new city,
بمجرد وصولنا إلى المدينة الجديدة،
everything will be okay.
كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام.
Let me.
دعني.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Qin Lang.
تشين لانج.
I'm married now.
أنا متزوج الآن.
And I've decided to move away
وقد قررت الرحيل
to start over.
للبدء من جديد.
I sold the old house.
بعتُ المنزل القديم.
I transferred all the money to Cheng Yi-chen's account.
لقد حولت كل الأموال إلى حساب تشنغ يي تشن.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
I'm leaving Cheng Yi-chen to you.
أترك أمر تشنغ يي تشن لك.
For the time being,
في الوقت الحاضر،
I'll contact you if I need anything.
سأتصل بك إذا احتجت إلى أي شيء.
Don't try to find me,
لا تحاول البحث عني،
and don't worry about me.
ولا تقلق عليّ.
Lu Feng will definitely come looking for me again.
سيأتي لو فنغ بالتأكيد للبحث عني مرة أخرى.
Xiao Chen.
شياو تشن.
And I...
وأنا...
I really don't know how to face him.
لا أعرف حقاً كيف أواجهه.
You should try to stay away from him, too.
يجب عليكِ أن تحاولي الابتعاد عنه أيضاً.
Xiao Chen.
شياو تشن.
Mr. Lu.
السيد صن
Where's Xiao Chen?
أين شياو تشن؟
He quit.
لقد استقال.
Even if you find him, what then?
حتى لو وجدته، ماذا بعد ذلك؟
From the moment he got married,
منذ لحظة زواجه،
he already gave up on you.
لقد تخلى عنك بالفعل.
Lu Feng.
لو فنغ.
You need to understand.
عليك أن تفهم.
If you truly want to be the master of your own destiny,
إذا كنت ترغب حقاً في أن تكون سيد مصيرك،
you have to learn to bide your time.
عليك أن تتعلم كيف تنتظر الوقت المناسب.
Wait until you're strong enough to fly.
انتظر حتى تصبح قوياً بما يكفي للطيران.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
Get some rest.
خذ قسطاً من الراحة.
Five years later.
بعد خمس سنوات.
Let's begin.
لنبدأ.
Okay.
تمام.
According to our market research,
وفقًا لأبحاثنا السوقية،
Well,
حسنًا،
I'll be going then.
سأذهب حينها.
Leaving? I'm going home too.
هل ستغادر؟ أنا ذاهب إلى المنزل أيضاً.
He's been waiting for you.
لقد كان ينتظرك.
Mr. Cheng.
السيد تشنغ
After all, we are still legally married.
في النهاية، ما زلنا متزوجين قانونياً.
This kind of behavior...
هذا النوع من السلوك...
is disrespectful to all three of us.
هذا يُعدّ عدم احترام لنا جميعاً.
Let's wait until we have time to finalize the divorce.
لننتظر حتى يتوفر لدينا الوقت لإنهاء إجراءات الطلاق.
Yichen.
ييتشن.
I think it's time for us to move on.
أعتقد أن الوقت قد حان لننتقل إلى مرحلة أخرى.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I've held you back all these years.
لقد أعاقتك طوال هذه السنوات.
Who's holding who back?
من يعيق من؟
If it weren't for you these past few years,
لولاك في السنوات القليلة الماضية،
I wouldn't have been able to establish myself at the company so quickly.
لم أكن لأتمكن من ترسيخ مكانتي في الشركة بهذه السرعة.
Besides,
بجانب،
if it weren't for these five years,
لولا هذه السنوات الخمس،
how would I have known...
كيف لي أن أعرف...
that we're actually better off as friends?
هل يعني ذلك أننا في الواقع أفضل حالاً كأصدقاء؟
We'll always be friends.
سنبقى أصدقاء إلى الأبد.
I think so too.
أعتقد ذلك أيضاً.
A new generation of entrepreneurs
جيل جديد من رواد الأعمال
who grew up in the internet age
الذين نشأوا في عصر الإنترنت
are reshaping philanthropy
إنهم يعيدون تشكيل العمل الخيري
with their unique and innovative thinking.
بفضل تفكيرهم الفريد والمبتكر.
Today,
اليوم،
we have the honor of interviewing a pioneering entrepreneur,
يشرفنا إجراء مقابلة مع رائد أعمال متميز،
the founder of Feng Yang Technology,
مؤسس شركة Feng Yang Technology،
Mr. Lu Feng.
السيد لو فنغ
We've invited him to talk to us about
لقد دعوناه للتحدث إلينا حول
his philanthropic philosophy.
فلسفته الخيرية.
Hello, everyone.
أهلا بالجميع.
I'm Lu Feng, the founder of FC Company.
أنا لو فينغ، مؤسس شركة FC.
FC Company has always been a leader
لطالما كانت شركة FC رائدة
in emerging technologies.
في التقنيات الناشئة.
And giving back to the community
ورد الجميل للمجتمع
is one of our company's core principles.
يُعدّ هذا أحد المبادئ الأساسية لشركتنا.
[After all these years he stays looking up Lu Feng on the internet]
[بعد كل هذه السنوات، ما زال يبحث عن لو فنغ على الإنترنت]
You want to quit?
هل تريد الاستقالة؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Is it because we got divorced?
هل السبب هو طلاقنا؟
No.
لا.
Then why?
فلماذا؟
You've worked so hard to establish yourself at the company.
لقد بذلت جهداً كبيراً لتثبيت نفسك في الشركة.
Have you been too stressed or tired lately?
هل كنت تعاني من ضغط أو إرهاق شديدين مؤخراً؟
No, Zhuo Lan.
لا، تشو لان.
I just...
أنا فقط...
want to do something else.
أريد أن أفعل شيئًا آخر.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I respect your decision.
أحترم قرارك.
But remember,
لكن تذكر،
no matter what,
مهما حدث،
there will always be a place for you here.
سيكون لك مكان هنا دائماً.
Hello, who are you looking for?
مرحباً، من تبحث عنه؟
I'm looking for Lu Feng.
أبحث عن لو فنغ.
Do you have an appointment?
هل لديك موعد؟
No.
لا.
But I'm an old...
لكنني رجل عجوز...
friend of his.
صديقه.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
You can't go in without an appointment.
لا يمكنك الدخول بدون موعد مسبق.
I really am his friend.
أنا صديقه حقاً.
Another 'friend'.
صديق آخر.
Ever since the boss was in the news,
منذ أن أصبح المدير حديث الساعة،
people claiming to be his friend have been showing up one after another.
بدأ الناس الذين يدّعون أنهم أصدقاؤه بالظهور واحداً تلو الآخر.
Thinking they can just come and go as they please.
يظنون أن بإمكانهم القدوم والذهاب كما يحلو لهم.
Do they think this is a public market?
هل يعتقدون أن هذا سوق عام؟
If you're really his friend, why didn't you make an appointment yourself?
إذا كنت صديقه حقاً، فلماذا لم تحدد موعداً بنفسك؟
Hey.
يا.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Did you hurt your leg?
هل أصبت ساقك؟
Maybe we should go to the hospital to get it checked out.
ربما ينبغي علينا الذهاب إلى المستشفى لفحصه.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Is something wrong with your laptop?
هل هناك مشكلة في جهاز الكمبيوتر المحمول الخاص بك؟
It's broken.
إنه معطل.
I have very important files on it that I haven't exported.
لدي ملفات مهمة للغاية عليه لم أقم بتصديرها.
How about this?
ما رأيك بهذا؟
Let's go to the hospital first. I know how to fix computers.
لنذهب إلى المستشفى أولاً. أعرف كيف أصلح أجهزة الكمبيوتر.
Get in the car, I'll take a look for you.
اركب السيارة، سألقي نظرة من أجلك.
Did it get wet?
هل تبلل؟
Yes.
نعم.
It got wet last night.
لقد تبلل المكان الليلة الماضية.
I called customer service,
اتصلت بخدمة العملاء،
and they told me to leave it upside down overnight.
وقالوا لي أن أتركه مقلوباً طوال الليل.
They said it would be fine the next day.
قالوا إن الأمور ستكون على ما يرام في اليوم التالي.
But now it won't turn on.
لكنها الآن لا تعمل.
The motherboard is probably corroded.
من المحتمل أن تكون اللوحة الأم متآكلة.
It can't be fixed in this condition.
لا يمكن إصلاحه في هذه الحالة.
Then what do I do?
إذن ماذا أفعل؟
My thesis that I've been writing for a month is still on it.
لا تزال أطروحتي التي أكتبها منذ شهر قيد الإعداد.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
We can go to a repair shop
يمكننا الذهاب إلى ورشة إصلاح
and just retrieve the data from the storage drive.
ثم استرجع البيانات من وحدة التخزين.
Come on, let's go to the hospital first.
هيا بنا، لنذهب إلى المستشفى أولاً.
Let's go to the repair shop first.
لنذهب إلى ورشة الإصلاح أولاً.
Okay.
تمام.
By the way, what's your name?
بالمناسبة، ما اسمك؟
My name is Ke Lo.
اسمي كي لو.
Ke Lo.
ذا لو.
Then I'll see you again tomorrow.
إذن، سأراك غداً.
Okay, goodbye.
حسنًا، إلى اللقاء.
I've transferred all your files to this hard drive.
لقد نقلت جميع ملفاتك إلى هذا القرص الصلب.
I asked around.
سألت بعض الأشخاص.
It would cost several thousand to repair the laptop.
سيكلف إصلاح الكمبيوتر المحمول عدة آلاف.
I don't think it's worth it.
لا أعتقد أن الأمر يستحق ذلك.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
As long as I have my files.
طالما أن ملفاتي معي.
Are you still looking for a job?
هل ما زلت تبحث عن وظيفة؟
Yeah.
نعم.
How's your leg? Does it still hurt?
كيف حال ساقك؟ هل ما زالت تؤلمك؟
It's fine.
لا بأس.
It doesn't hurt at all.
لا يسبب أي ألم على الإطلاق.
Maybe you should still go to the hospital to get it checked.
ربما لا يزال يتعين عليك الذهاب إلى المستشفى لإجراء الفحص.
Look, it's really fine.
انظر، الأمر جيد حقاً.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
I know the boss of a tech company,
أعرف رئيس شركة تقنية،
and they're hiring right now.
وهم يوظفون حالياً.
You're so capable.
أنت تتمتع بقدرات كبيرة.
You'll definitely get the job.
ستحصل على الوظيفة بالتأكيد.
I took the liberty of
لقد أخذت على عاتقي
sending them the resume from your back seat.
إرسال السيرة الذاتية إليهم من المقعد الخلفي لسيارتك.
How do you know I'm capable?
كيف تعرف أنني كفؤ؟
Isn't it obvious?
أليس هذا واضحاً؟
My laptop...
حاسوبي المحمول...
you knew what was wrong with it right away.
عرفتَ ما الخطأ فيه على الفور.
Plus, you're kind,
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، أنت لطيف،
upright,
منتصبة،
and responsible. Okay, okay.
ومسؤول. حسناً، حسناً.
Don't overdo it.
لا تبالغ في ذلك.
I'm serious.
أنا جادة.
Why don't we go check it out now?
لماذا لا نذهب لنلقي نظرة عليه الآن؟
Let's go, let's go.
هيا بنا، هيا بنا.
We're here.
نحن هنا.
This is it.
هذا هو الأمر.
The boss you know... his name is Lu Feng?
الرئيس الذي تعرفه... اسمه لو فنغ؟
How did you know?
كيف عرفت؟
This place isn't right for me.
هذا المكان لا يناسبني.
You should at least meet him before you decide.
ينبغي عليك على الأقل مقابلته قبل أن تتخذ قرارك.
No.
لا.
I already told my...
لقد أخبرتُ بالفعل...
I already told Mr. Lu.
لقد أخبرت السيد لو بالفعل.
And he's very impressed with you.
وهو معجب بك جداً.
He wants to interview you himself.
يريد أن يجري معك مقابلة بنفسه.
Normally, this kind of thing
عادةً، هذا النوع من الأشياء
is handled by his subordinates.
يتولى مرؤوسوه الأمر.
He knows it's me?
هل يعرف أنني أنا؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Come on, let's go.
هيا بنا، لنذهب.
Nervous?
متوتر؟
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Have a good chat. Mr. Lu.
أتمنى لك محادثة طيبة. سيد لو.
Yichen.
ييتشن.
Long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
I thought it was just someone with the same name.
ظننت أنه مجرد شخص يحمل نفس الاسم.
I can't believe it's really you.
لا أصدق أنك أنت حقاً.
Have a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
I didn't expect you to be in Xincheng too.
لم أتوقع أن تكون في شينتشنغ أيضاً.
I thought you would've come to find me sooner.
كنت أظن أنك ستأتي للعثور عليّ عاجلاً.
I did look for you.
لقد بحثت عنك.
But I didn't have an appointment.
لكن لم يكن لدي موعد.
So...
لذا...
So you found Ke Lo.
إذن، لقد وجدت كي لو.
Using him was a pretty clever move.
كان استخدامه خطوة ذكية للغاية.
I didn't use Ke Lo. I...
لم أستخدم Ke Lo. أنا...
Ke Lo is just a kid.
كي لو مجرد طفل.
He's naive
إنه ساذج
and very enthusiastic.
ومتحمس للغاية.
Most importantly,
والأهم من ذلك،
he's very close to me.
إنه قريب جداً مني.
It really could make things a lot easier for you.
قد يُسهّل ذلك الأمور عليك كثيراً.
By the way.
بالمناسبة.
Ke Lo said you wanted to work at my company.
قال كي لو إنك تريد العمل في شركتي.
Are you still at your old job?
هل ما زلت تعمل في وظيفتك القديمة؟
At my company,
في شركتي،
for an employee at your level,
بالنسبة لموظف في مستواك الوظيفي،
the salary is usually around...
الراتب عادة ما يكون حوالي...
No.
لا.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Worried the salary is too low?
هل تشعر بالقلق من أن الراتب منخفض للغاية؟
How about this.
ما رأيك بهذا؟
Since we're old classmates,
بما أننا زملاء دراسة قدامى،
you can name your price.
يمكنك تحديد السعر الذي تريده.
Don't be shy.
لا تخجل.
As long as it's within a reasonable range,
طالما أنه ضمن نطاق معقول،
I'll be sure to meet it.
سأحرص على مقابلته.
That won't be necessary.
لن يكون ذلك ضرورياً.
I've already found a job.
لقد وجدت وظيفة بالفعل.
Then what are you here for today?
إذن، ما سبب وجودك هنا اليوم؟
If there's nothing else,
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر،
please don't waste my time.
من فضلك لا تضيع وقتي.
I have a client meeting soon.
لدي اجتماع مع أحد العملاء قريباً.
Then I'll be going.
ثم سأذهب.
So? How did it go?
إذن؟ كيف سارت الأمور؟
I really don't want to work here.
لا أرغب حقاً في العمل هنا.
Why?
لماذا؟
Is it the salary?
هل السبب هو الراتب؟
Or some other reason?
أم لسبب آخر؟
Ke Lo.
ذا لو.
Come in.
ادخل.